[
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is peaceful and reliable, what is their strongest humor?",
    "answer": "phlegm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is outgoing and carefree what is their strongest humor?",
    "answer": "blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is restless and impulsive what is their strongest humor?",
    "answer": "yellow bile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is reserved and pessimistic what is their strongest humor?",
    "answer": "black bile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is struck with insanity what humor should be leeched?",
    "answer": "phlegm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is struck with gallbladder attacks what humor should be leeched?",
    "answer": "yellow bile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is struck with spleen weakness what humor should be leeched?",
    "answer": "black bile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood, phlegm, yellow bile and black bile. The four bodily humors determine a person temperament and illness; if a person is struck with heart mummers what humor should be leeched?",
    "answer": "blood"
  }
]

//ARCHIVED RIDDLES 'Riddles are thematic and map to the game IP'
//[
//  {
//    "question": "I speak without a mouth and hear without ears. I have no body but come alive with the wind. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "echo"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "What has keys but can't open locks, and is filled with notes, yet remains silent? ",
//    "answer": "piano"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I am taken from a mine and shut up in a wooden case, from which I am never released, and yet I am used by almost every person. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "pencil"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I am the beginning of the end, the end of every place. I am the beginning of eternity, the end of time and space. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "the letter e"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I am taken from a mine and shut up in a wooden case, from which I am never released, and yet I am used by almost every person. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "clock"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "The more you take, the more you leave behind. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "footsteps"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I have cities, but no houses. I have mountains, but no trees. I have water, but no fish. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "map"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I am not alive, but I grow; I don't have lungs, but I need air; I don't have a mouth, but water kills me. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "fire"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "What comes once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in a thousand years? ",
//    "answer": "the letter m"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "I am an odd number; take away a letter, and I become even. What am I? ",
//    "answer": "seven"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "A vessel have I, that is round as a pear, moist in the middle, surrounded with hair; and often it happens, that water flows there.",
//    "answer": "eye"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "What is the sister of the sun, though made for the night? The fire causes her tears to fall, and when she is near dying they cut off her head.",
//    "answer": "candle"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "What speaks in all languages in his riding, and his mouth spits the poison of life or death? It is silent when it rests, and is deaf like a boy or one of the poor.",
//    "answer": "pen"
//  },
//  {
//    "question": "An eater lacking mouth and even maw; yet trees and beasts to it are daily bread. Well fed it thrives and shows a lively life, but give it water and you do it dead. ",
//    "answer": "fire"
//  }
//]